{
    "id": "bc64b6a3ae744d919de4bbc29caa1381",
    "title": "Passives Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The walls ........................................ painted.",
            "description": "The passive form of the present continuous is used to talk about ongoing actions and situations.",
            "answers": [
                "are still",
                "are still being"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6bc8c02e41d6433e84dccb33ff9bb086"
        },
        {
            "question": "This bag ................................... of leather.",
            "description": "We use the simple present to talk about materials used for making things.",
            "answers": [
                "is made",
                "was made",
                "has been made"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "84a2a174e70c4eeb9f2b48ffe358c640"
        },
        {
            "question": "The smugglers .......................................",
            "description": "In the present perfect, the passive verb form is: has/have + been + past participle form of the verb.",
            "answers": [
                "have caught",
                "have been caught",
                "is caught"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c9fbcc72f1a44c1a836b0926709f4ecb"
        },
        {
            "question": "All of them ......................................",
            "description": "In the present perfect, the passive verb form is: has/have + been + past participle form of the verb.",
            "answers": [
                "have invited",
                "have been invited",
                "have been inviting"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "155ebd8de08d4a7fb24896a553d722b1"
        },
        {
            "question": "The boys ...................................... for their performance.",
            "description": "In the simple past, the passive form is made by putting was/were before the past participle form of the verb.",
            "answers": [
                "were praised",
                "were praising",
                "have praised"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "4a4cfb46b5e847bda725e06598bebf95"
        },
        {
            "question": "She ................................... by the manager.",
            "description": "In the simple past, the passive form is made by putting was/were before the past participle form of the verb.",
            "answers": [
                "has sacked",
                "was sacked",
                "was sacking"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a3c47afa268042a383653f8f4c4a4ff8"
        },
        {
            "question": "The suspect ..................................... by the police.",
            "description": "We use the present continuous passive to talk about ongoing actions and situations.",
            "answers": [
                "is interrogated",
                "is interrogating",
                "is being interrogated"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "8bc212b353004aeaa7d721cfc705c089"
        },
        {
            "question": "He ....................................  to the post of manager.",
            "description": "In the simple future, the passive form is made by putting will + be before the past participle form of the verb.",
            "answers": [
                "will promote",
                "will be promoting",
                "will be promoted"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "ea9193ed0c3547dd97f716a5cf79705d"
        },
        {
            "question": "She ........................................ to resign.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "forced",
                "was forcing",
                "was forced"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "52e8d0c38bc247ff8c34c8458d5db59c"
        },
        {
            "question": "The roof ................................... by the masons.",
            "description": "The passive form of the present continuous is used to talk about ongoing actions and situations. ",
            "answers": [
                "is repaired",
                "is being repaired",
                "has been repairing"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0577b58f7d7a44859fcb2dc2ce702401"
        },
        {
            "question": "These tablets ....................................... with food.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "must take",
                "must be taken",
                "must be taking"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ca5d017d67154e30b62eb9801959dd91"
        },
        {
            "question": "It .................................... from New Zealand.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is importing",
                "is imported",
                "has imported"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ec57fd3e77e54b5aa156a685280c4afe"
        }
    ]
}